John Lyin

WEB DEVELOPER

Profile

Enterprising Computer Science student with growing professional experience and desire to move into tech companies. I would love to partner alongside a company that will allow me to apply my education in problem solving and web development.

Education

Computer Science, Indiana University/Purdue University at Indianapolis, Indianapolis

AUGUST 2016 - DECEMBER 2020

Eleven Fifty Academy, Indianapolis

APRIL 2020 - JULY 2020

MAY 2020 - MAY 2020

Courses

Database Design, IUPUI

AUGUST 2019 - DECEMBER 2019

Project Management, IUPUI

AUGUST 2018 - DECEMBER 2018

Data Structures & Algorithms, IUPUI

AUGUST 2017 - DECEMBER 2017

Advanced database Programming, IUPUI

JANUARY 2020 - MAY 2020

Client Side Web Programming, IUPUI

JANUARY 2019 - MAY 2019

Employment History

Teacher Assistant, Indiana University-Purdue University of Indianapolis, Indianapolis

JANUARY 2019 - MAY 2020

- Assist in instruction, grading, and mentoring.
- Customize logical Data Models for the students.
- Inspect students' SQL for their projects.

Teacher Assistant, St.Mark Catholic School, Indianapolis

APRIL 2017 - JANUARY 2019

- · Assisted in instruction, grading, and mentoring.
- Translated in Parent Conference Meeting (English Burmese).
- Managed the students' behavior.

Details

(317) 437-2710 jthang3@gmail.com

Links

Linkedin

<u>Github</u>

<u>Portfolio</u>

Skills

Python

JavaScript

HTML5/CSS3

Java

C++

SQL

Node.js

pgAdmin

jQuery

Bootstrap 4

Git